I don't think there's any celebrity on the planet that's done more damage to their reputation
of the last couple years than Will Smith. His name has become synonymous with cringe.
He discovers new ways to embarrass himself that most scientists didn't even think possible.
It's baffling because the call is coming from inside the house. He is the one that is making
the conscious decision to open himself up like Goatsy for everyone to take a peek inside,
and it is irresistible to point and laugh at what we find. He is the human manifestation of
asbestos, where asbestos was once like this really celebrated thing but over time as more
information came out about it, people realized, oh this isn't very good. That's what's been
happening with Will Smith. I remember growing up, he was like an idol to so many people,
and over the last I'd say like five to maybe like six or seven years, he has just become laughable.
It just seems like he's stuck in a perpetual humiliation ritual of his own making,
and now his new thing is promoting his tour with AI images of concert goers. So I don't know how
many of you know this Will Smith is on tour right now. He's back making music and he's got some
finger wiggling boner jams like I like pretty girls, and he's on tour right now and he just
posted on his official YouTube channel a clip that features an AI generated crowd. I had to mute
the audio obviously, but there are definitely real people that are going to his tour. I don't think
the number is as great as him and his team want it to be, so for their promotional material for
the tour, they resort to showing AI generated crowds cheering and going ballistic for Will Smith,
and it's blatantly obvious that it's AI. This is some turbo insecure activity right here,
like this is an actual like midlife crisis meltdown moment where he's like the numbers aren't where
I wanted to be. Let's go ahead and fudge it with some AI generated crowd reactions that love me.
It's so fucking odd. I imagine you can see a lot of AI here already. There's of course real people
that are spliced in here too, but just take a look at this for example. This clip has me feeling like
I hit the crack pipe while on ayahuasca like look at this image. Like here, we'll just start zooming
in in a couple of different places. Like here, look over in this direction. What an entire nation,
what the hell are you even looking at when it comes to this? Who is this? Looks like the scary monster
that would chase you around in an amnesial horror game. All the people around her two are all
anamorphing. If you go in any direction in this section of the video, this is exactly what you'll find.
Over on this side of the freak show in the Sea of Monsters, things get really weird. Everyone
has completely blended into some like amorphous blob. There's one guy here in front of this
gray shirt man that looks like Asmengold got hit with like an anvil that flattened him. And then
if you go above him, you'll find like a Neanderthal with his arms pumped up and Jeffrey Epstein taking
cover behind him. It is clearly AI and it's very reminiscent of early AI video footage like with
Will Smith eating spaghetti. It's like one to one with that because especially in that like last shot
there, everyone in the crowd looks identical to that painting you see in every horror game,
Saturn devouring his son. It is crazy just how bad the AI crowd is here in his own promotional video.
He is just shamelessly using an AI crowd to promote his tour and how like emotional it's been.
Like this is why I do it for this. And then it's like that lady that has like 45 different
hands while everyone around her is getting fucking morphed into some giant amalgamation of flesh
and bone. It's so pathetic. I really cannot wrap my head around how nobody on his team nor
himself saw this and thought probably a bad idea. People are going to know this is AI. Like I
don't know how that notion never once crossed their minds because again, it's not even like it's
good AI where it's like indistinguishable from reality. It is clearly an AI crowd in a lot of these
shots and that makes the tour look so bad. It makes it feel like nobody is going. That's the
perception now. I guess no one's going to Will Smith's tours because they can't even find
enough crowd shots to fill a fucking 58 second promotional video for it. I really cannot believe
that he would be in such a bad state financially that he would have to resort to something like this.
Like he was like one of the biggest actors in Hollywood for so so long. Like top tier A
list actor. He's got to have unfathomable wealth. Why is he doing this? Like one has to wonder what
has brought him to this and like the endless amounts of embarrassing shit that he himself won't
stop talking about. Like I'm not just going to regurgitate all of his past scandals and like
weird behavior and weird stuff but he himself loves to bring that kind of shit up. Seems to like
Tawalo in that. Like he plays around in the big pin of past controversies proudly. So even years later,
he will bring up that incident with Chris Rock where he went on stage and slapped the shit out of him
like he was trying to fucking neuralize him via the five fingers to the face. Like he is the one
that will bring up things like the slap and all of that. It makes no sense. It feels like he loves
it when people are laughing at him as opposed to with him. I don't get it. I really don't know.
Anyway, just found this silly one in the app about it a bit. That's it. See you.